Samir Prajapati

Kathmandu, Bāgmatī, Nepal

bullseye405@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/samir-prajapati-b9b589174

Summary

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with React, React Native, Laravel, MySQL, PostgreSQL and wide range of programming utilities.

Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements.

Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 5+ years of related experience.

Experience



React Developer

Appraisal Inbox

May 2022 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Responsible for the development and maintenance of frontend

React Engineer

InfoDevelopers Pvt. Ltd.

Feb 2022 - Aug 2023 (1 year 7 months)

Full Stack Developer

Auxfin Development Nepal

Mar 2021 - Feb 2022 (1 year)

Ϧ Full Stack Developer

Biramedia

Feb 2021 - Jul 2021 (6 months)

Developer

Auxfin Development Nepal

Apr 2020 - Mar 2021 (1 year)

Junior Developer

Auxfin Development Nepal

Apr 2019 - Mar 2020 (1 year)

Intern

Auxfin Development Nepal

Dec 2018 - Mar 2019 (4 months)

Education

National College Of Computer Studies

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2014 - 2019

Capitol Hill College

Higher Secondary (+2), Science 2012 - 2014

Saraswoti Boarding Higher Secondary School

Skills

Tailwind CSS • Flux • Object Oriented Design • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Databases • Computer Science • HTML • Software Development • Full-Stack Development • Front-End Development